{
    "subject": "resource/Kiss_Me_Good-Bye",
    "predicate": "ontology/musicalArtist",
    "object": "resource/Angela_Aki",
    "human_readable": "The musical artist behind Kiss Me Good-Bye is Angela Aki.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9215100407600403,
            "question": "Who is the musical artist behind the song Kiss Me Good-Bye?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6895427107810974,
            "question": "Angela Aki is a musician. What is she known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6462023258209229,
            "question": "What genre of music does Angela Aki perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6230615377426147,
            "question": "Tell me about Angela Aki's musical work."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48414146900177,
            "question": "What song is Angela Aki known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47295746207237244,
            "question": "What song popularized Angela Aki?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4622732400894165,
            "question": "Is Angela Aki a singer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45014408230781555,
            "question": "Is Kiss Me Good-Bye a famous song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43310150504112244,
            "question": "Who sings the song Kiss Me Good-Bye?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37746307253837585,
            "question": "Can you name a song by Angela Aki?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The musical artist behind Kiss Me Good-Bye is Angela Aki.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1899_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who sings the song Kiss Me Good-Bye?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1899_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Kiss Me Good-Bye a famous song?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1899_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Angela Aki a singer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1899_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1899_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1899_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1899_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1899_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1899_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1899_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1899_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1899_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1899_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1899_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents mention that Angela Aki performed the song \"Kiss Me Good-Bye\" for the Final Fantasy XII soundtrack, and another document confirms this by listing her as the lyricist and arranger of the song."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}